[{"answer": "Nothing.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "What do you think -- if your brain path for this kind of thing, what can we confidently predict?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "LITZER: It probably would have been but I think they've assumed from day one that Mitt Romney is going to be the Republican presidential nominee.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Would that have been a good thing for the president?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "Ron Paul is not going anywhere, Piers.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "If either of those candidates pulled out, where would their votes go?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "Well, I'm feeling like it was a big win in Arizona and we're just really pleased that the people rallied around the man that we believe can move forward and beat President Obama.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "So how are you feeling overall about it?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Well, I think that the bottom line is that he's -- you know, he's leading in the race.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "What would you be advising him to do?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "Now, Piers, you don't know what I was saying.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Is that what you want to see from Mitt Romney when the battle royale starts?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "Oh, no.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Just to be serious, I mean if Mitt Romney does win and is the nominee and he gets to take on Barack Obama, should he be making some kind of advantage of the apparent thin-skinned that you've identified?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I will be honest with you.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "So I mean he's got it in him, isn't he, to really stick the knife in?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I originally, I think, bought into the conventional wisdom that Governor Romney was the strongest candidate against Barack Obama.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "So why did you switch?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think Governor Romney can be very happy with his performance in Michigan.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "I mean given that Mitt Romney has won both in Arizona and Michigan tonight, I mean, do you feel a bit that guy that put everything on red in Vegas and then came out black?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "There's a great deal of enthusiasm.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "What are you going to do about that?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Well, I think -- I think Senator Santorum has explained exactly what he meant.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "Did President Kennedy's speech about the separation of church and state make you want to throw up and do you think it's snobbish for the president of the United States to want people to go to college?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "It's not clear at all what the motive is, what the motive was.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "Are you any clearer about what the motive may have been for this senseless killing?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "No, not at all, Piers.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "Is there a family rift about it?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "Well, I think, I think Ohio is going to be a lot like we saw with Michigan over the course of the last week and I would suggest to your viewers that -- that they just throw out any poll they have seen so far.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "What is your sense about the way it's going?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "They absolutely do.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Do those things really matter on the ground in somewhere like Michigan?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "Well, I think it -- I think it could be helpful but I'll tell you what.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "How damaging is a prolonged race or could it be like the Democrat race four years ago where actually it ends up being quite helpful?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "I have not changed my mind, Piers.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "Have you changed your mind?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "Well, no.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "Have you changed your mind?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "Well, look, if you think about what being bankrupt is, it isn't going out of business.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "So I mean, are you in possession of information that I'm not in possession of?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "Yes, but it's not -- it's not a success.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "I mean, it's not a winning proposition for any candidate in a presidential election, is it?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "If I could just jump in and...", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "Well -- yes?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "The professor always has a way back in.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "You know, has he got a way back?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "Oh, Newt'll probably think it's enough, but he should probably try and win one or two more on that same day.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Would it be enough, even if he wins in Georgia?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "Well, it -- now at RealClearPolitics, it's up to 20 percent, when it was down in single digits before.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "Is it a real possibility?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "You know, it's really hard to see who that person would be.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "I mean, is there anybody realistically who's going to stick their neck out now and take on Barack Obama in an election that many think they couldn't win?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "Sarah...", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "Who's at the top of the ticket?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Well, there was enough...", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "What media scrutiny?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "One of the other...", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "You also don't chose someone at the last minute as your potential nominee who hasn't been thoroughly vetted for a while by the media, do you?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "Who?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "Oh, boy, you know, I had predicted Hillary Clinton in 2008, so I'm not sure my prediction is worth much.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "Amy?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "I'm voting for you, Piers.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "Carol?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not going to, you know, comment on the details of what happened with the Romney campaign, but I was very honored to be able to work with him.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "Why did you and Mitt Romney part company just after the Florida debate, where by common consent, you'd got him back on track?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, I think, you know, this race has been all about momentum, and there's been a lag between some of the contests.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "Why is he still struggling to really cement this front-runner position, do you think?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, I think it's the personal side.", "docId": "120228pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "I mean, knowing Mitt Romney as you do, what is it that he's struggling to get out there about his character, his personality, that perhaps he isn't selling well enough yet?", "qSentId": 622}]